

About Me

I am a student at SMKS Wikrama Bogor, majoring in Software Development and Games. I have a strong interest in IT and I also have some experience in creating front-end website programming projects. I enjoy selfimprovement, building relationships, and exploring new things.

Skills

- Web Design
- Team leadership
- Calm under preassure
- Confident
- Quick learner

Language

English

SYAIKHANI GIFFA INDRAWAN

Web Developer

LinkedIn

+6287781045812

linkedin.com/in/syaikhanigiffa

Phone

Email

giffasyaikhani2005@gmail.com

Address

Jl. Raya Puncak Gg. Asparagus Ds. Cibeureum Rt 01 Rw 02 No. 36 Kec. Cisarua, Kab. Bogor, 16750

Experience

Student

Jul 2021 - Current

SMK Wikrama Bogor

- Participant with project work as Front-end Developer.
- Contribute training Cybersecurity sub-batch 2.
- Contribute culture exchange TOMODACHI PROGRAM AirPangea.
- Training with industries for UI/UX, and mobile development with Flutter.
- Developed website using git colaboration.
- Developed E-Book using Laravel.
- Developed E-Commerce using Laravel.
- Joined Graphic Design club to build adobe Potoshop skill, Figma skill, relationships and connections with students.
- Joined Python club to build basic data analyst skills

Web Developer Intern

Jan 2023 - Jul 2023

PT Hexaon Business Mitrasindo

- Developed Fraud Detection System sites as front-end using Angular.
- Designed and developed website for customers relationship management using Laravel.
- Participated in pre-project analysis as Front-end.
- Participated as part of Front-end company team.
- · Communicated clearly with web development teams, ascertaining daily tasks and completing to exact direction.
- Slicing website designed by Senior.

Education

SMK Wikrama Bogor

Jul 2021 - Current

Pengembangan Perangkat Lunak dan Gim



Tentang Saya

Saya adalah seorang siswa di SMK Wikrama Bogor, jurusan Pengembangan Perangkat Lunak dan Gim. Saya memiliki minat yang kuat dalam bidang IT dan juga memiliki beberapa pengalaman dalam membuat proyek pemrograman website sebagai front-end developer. Saya menikmati peningkatan diri, membangun hubungan, dan menjelajahi hal-hal baru.

Skills

- Merancang Website
- Team Leadership
- Tenang dibawah tekanan
- Percaya diri
- Cepat Belajar

Bahasa

Inggris

SYAIKHANI GIFFA INDRAWAN

Web Developer

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/syaikhanigiffa

Telepon

+6287781045812

Email

giffasyaikhani2005@gmail.com

Alamat

Jl. Raya Puncak Gg. Asparagus Ds. Cibeureum Rt 01 Rw 02 No. 36 Kec. Cisarua, Kab. Bogor, 16750

Pengalaman

Murid

Jul 2021 - Sekarang

SMK Wikrama Bogor

- Berpartisipasi dalam proyek sebagai Front-end Developer.
- Berkontribusi dalam pelatihan sub-batch 2 Keamanan Siber.
- Berkontribusi dalam pertukaran budaya PROGRAM TOMODACHI AirPangea.
- Melakukan pelatihan dengan industri untuk UI/UX, dan pengembangan mobile dengan Flutter.
- Mengembangkan website menggunakan kolaborasi git.
- Mengembangkan E-Book menggunakan Laravel.
- Mengembangkan E-Commerce menggunakan Laravel.
- Bergabung dengan klub Desain Grafis untuk membangun keterampilan Adobe Photoshop, keterampilan Figma, hubungan, dan koneksi dengan sesama siswa.
- Bergabung dengan klub Python untuk membangun keterampilan dasar analis data.

Magang sebagai Web Developer PT Hexaon Business Mitrasindo

Jan 2023 - Jul 2023

- Mengembangkan situs Sistem Deteksi Penipuan sebagai front-end menggunakan Angular.
- Merancang dan mengembangkan website untuk manajemen hubungan pelanggan menggunakan Laravel.
- Berpartisipasi dalam analisis pra-proyek sebagai Front-end.
- Menjadi bagian dari tim perusahaan Front-end.
- Berkomunikasi dengan jelas dengan tim pengembangan web, memastikan tugas-tugas harian dan menyelesaikannya sesuai arahan.
- Slicing website yang dirancang oleh Senior.

Pendidikan

SMK Wikrama Bogor

Jul 2021 - Sekarang

Pengembangan Perangkat Lunak dan Gim